emersonecologics.com 2008-09-12

# Emerson Ecologics - Privacy Statement

---  
\----------------------------  
\----------------------------  
\----------------------------  
   
Search Newswire  
| 

Emerson Ecologics has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.  The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: www.emersonecologics.com **Information Automatically Logged**   
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site.  Your IP address is also used to gather general demographic information. **Cookies**   
Our Site uses cookies to deliver content specific to your interests.  We only use cookies to save your shopping cart items so that they are accessible upon checkout. **Registration Forms**   
Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name, e-mail, and postal address). Contact information from the registration forms is used to ship purchases and to provide information about our company.  The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the customer when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Unique identifiers such as Customer Id and Passwords are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user's identity, and for use as account numbers in our record system. **Order Forms**   
Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services.  We collect contact information (like their e-mail address), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), and unique identifiers (Customer ID). Contact information from the order forms is used to ship purchases and to provide information about our company.  The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the customer when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. Unique identifiers (Customer ID and Password) are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user's identity, and for use as account numbers in our record system. **Surveys**   
Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like e-mail address). Contact information from the surveys is used to ship purchases and to provide information about our company.  The customer's contact information is also used to send promotional material from some of our partners to our customers, and to get in touch with the customer when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. **External Links**   
This site contains links to other sites.  Emerson Ecologics is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. **Security**   
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.  All Shopping Cart transactions are conducted on a secure server, which means all information you enter will be encrypted.  Your personal information is only available to you once you log into our Site with your valid Customer ID and Password. **Choice/Opt-Out**   
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from us. 

  1. You can send e-mail to [cs@emersonecologics.com](mailto:cs@emersonecologics.com)
  2. You can send mail to the following postal address:  
7 Commerce Dr., Bedford, NH  03110 
  3. You can call the following telephone number: 1-800-654-4432

**Data Quality/Access**   
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: 

  1. You can send e-mail to [cs@emersonecologics.com](mailto:cs@emersonecologics.com)
  2. You can visit the following URL: [www.emersonecologics.com](http://www.emersonecologics.com/)
  3. You can send mail to the following postal address:  
7 Commerce Dr., Bedford, NH  03110 
  4. You can call the following telephone number: 1-800-654-4432

**Contacting the Web Site**   
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: [cs@emersonecologics.com](mailto:cs@emersonecologics.com) or call 1-800-654-4432. 

* These statements have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration. These products are not intended to diagnose, treat, cure or prevent any disease. 

Please read our privacy statement.  
Copyright © 1997-2008. Emerson Ecologics, LLC.  All rights reserved.  
phone: 1-800-654-4432  e-mail: [cs@emersonecologics.com](mailto:cs@emersonecologics.com)  

All or part of the web pages that constitute the Emerson Ecologics web site may not be copied and posted elsewhere or used for any other commercial purpose, without the expressed written consent of Emerson Ecologics. Violators will be prosecuted.
